Contact

nrenteria2@u.westcoastunive rsity.edu

www.linkedin.com/in/ nicolerenteria2 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Licensed Practical Nurse (LPN) Medical Office Nursing

Nicole Renteria

RN-BSN

Chino, California

Summary

New Grad RN and experienced Licensed Practical Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the medical practice industry. Skilled in Medical Office, Medicine, Science, and Nursing. Strong healthcare services professional with a BSN from West Coast University.

Experience

Sono Bello Registered Nurse March 2017 - Present (3 years 5 months) Ontario, California, United States

San Dimas Community Hospital Staff Nurse LVN June 2013 - March 2017 (3 years 10 months) San Dimas, California, United States

West Anaheim Extended Care Charge Nurse June 2008 - June 2013 (5 years 1 month) Anaheim, California, United States

Education

West Coast University
MSN, Nurse Educator · (2020 - 2022)

West Coast University
Bachelor of Science - BS, Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2018 - 2020)

Chaffey College

General Studies · (2016 - 2018)